<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<merger version="3"><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="main$Generated" generated="true" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~"><source path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res"/><source path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\build\generated\res\rs\debug"/><source path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\build\generated\res\resValues\debug"/></dataSet><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="main" generated-set="main$Generated" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~"><source path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res"><file name="dummy_mylocation_button_shadow" path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\drawable\dummy_mylocation_button_shadow.xml" qualifiers="" type="drawable"/><file name="dummy_my_location_button" path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\drawable\dummy_my_location_button.png" qualifiers="" type="drawable"/><file name="dummy_infowindow" path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\layout\dummy_infowindow.xml" qualifiers="" type="layout"/><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers=""><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Close</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Please replace \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' in the config.xml with your API Key!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">Google Maps Android API v2 is not available for some reason on this device.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">The application is miss-configured. This error is not recoverable and will be treated as fatal. The developer should look at the logs after this to determine more actionable information.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">An internal error of Google Play Services occurred. Please retry, and it should resolve the problem.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">You attempted to connect to the service with an invalid account name specified.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">The application is not licensed to the user. This error is not recoverable and will be treated as fatal.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">A network error occurred. Please retry, and it should resolve the problem.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">The installed version of Google Play services has been disabled on this device. Please turn on Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">The version of the Google Play services installed on this device is not authentic. Please update the Google Play Services from Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Google Play services is missing on this device. Please install the Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">The installed version of Google Play services is out of date. Please update the Google Play Services from Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">You attempted to connect to the service but you are not signed in. Please check the Google Play Services configuration</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Since this device does not have any location provider, this app can not detect your location.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Location service is disabled.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">Location service is rejected by user.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Can not detect your location. Try again.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-ar\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="ar"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">أغلق</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">مع مفتاح API الخاص بك \"GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\" يرجى استبدال config.xml في منصات </string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">غير متوفر لسبب ما على هذا الجهاز Google Maps Android API v2 </string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">تم تكوين التطبيق بشكل خاطئ. هذا الخطأ غير قابل للاسترداد وسيتم التعامل معه على أنه مميت. يجب على مطور البرامج النظر في السجلات بعد ذلك لتحديد مزيد من المعلومات القابلة للتنفيذ</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">يرجى إعادة المحاولة ، ويجب أن تحل المشكلة ، Google Play حدث خطأ داخلي في خدمات </string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">لقد حاولت الاتصال بالخدمة باسم حساب غير صالح</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">.التطبيق غير مرخص للمستخدم. هذا الخطأ غير قابل للاسترداد وسيتم التعامل معه على أنه مميت</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">.حدث خطأ في الشبكة. الرجاء المحاولة مرة أخرى ، ويجب أن تحل المشكلة</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled"> Google Play على هذا الجهاز. الرجاء تشغيل خدمات Google Play تم تعطيل الإصدار المثبت من خدمات</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">Google play من متجر Google Play المثبتة على هذا الجهاز غير أصلي. يرجى تحديث خدمات Google Play إصدار خدمات</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Google Play مفقودة على هذا الجهاز. الرجاء تثبيت خدمات Google Play خدمات </string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">Google Play من متجر Google Play قديم. يرجى تحديث خدمات Google Play الإصدار المثبت من خدمات </string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required"> Google Play لقد حاولت الاتصال بالخدمة ولكنك لم تسجل الدخول. يرجى التحقق من تكوين خدمات </string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">. نظرًا لأن هذا الجهاز لا يحتوي على أي موفر للموقع ، لا يمكن لهذا التطبيق اكتشاف موقعك</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">تم تعطيل خدمة الموقع</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">خدمة الموقع مرفوضة من قبل المستخدم</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location"> .لا يمكن الكشف عن موقعك. حاول ثانية </string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-da\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="da"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Zamknij</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Proszę zastąpić \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' w pliku config.xml własnym kluczem API!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">Google Maps Android API v2 .</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">Aplikacja posiada niepoprawną konfigurację. Tego błędu nie można odtworzyć i będzie on traktowany jako krytyczny. W celu uzyskania bardziej szczegółowych informacji programista powinien przejrzeć pliki z logami.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Wystąpił błąd wewnątrz usług Google Play. Ponowne uruchomienie powinno rozwiązać problem.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Próbę nawiązania połączenia z usługą nie powiodła się, z powodu nieprawidłowej nazwy konta.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">Aplikacja nie jest licencjonowana dla użytkownika. Tego błędu nie można odtworzyć i będzie on traktowany jako krytyczny.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Wystąpił błąd połączenia internetowego. Proszę spróbować ponownie.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">Zainstalowana wersja usług Google Play została wyłączona na urządzeniu. Proszę włączyć  usługi Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">Zainstalowana na urządzeniu wersja usług Google Play jest fałszywa. Proszę zaktualizować usługi Google Play ze sklepu Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Nie odnaleziono zainstalowanej wersji usług Google Play. Proszę zainstalować  usługi Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">Zainstalowana wersja usług Google Play jest przestarzała. Proszę zaktualizować usługi Google Play Services w sklepie Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Próbowano połączyć się z usługami Google Play nie będąc zalogowanym. Proszę sprawdzić konfigurację usług Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Na urządzeniu nie odnaleziono usług dostarczających położenie. Aplikacja nie będzie w stanie określić położenia.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Usługi lokalizacji są wyłączone.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">Zgoda na usługi lokalizacji została odrzucona przez użytkownika.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Nie można określić położenia. Spróbuj ponownie.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-de\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="de"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Schließen</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Bitte ersetzen Sie \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' unter config.xml durch Ihren API Key!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">Google Maps Android API v2 ist auf diesem Gerät aus einem unbekannten Grund nicht verfügbar.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">Die Anwendung ist falsch konfiguriert und kann nicht fortgefahren werden. Der Entwickler muss die Protokolle inspezieren, um weitere Informationen zu erhalten.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Ein interner Fehler der Google Play-Dienste ist aufgetreten. Bitte versuchen Sie es erneut.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Sie haben versucht, eine Verbindung zum Dienst mit einem ungültigen Kontonamen herzustellen.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">Die Anwendung ist für den Benutzer nicht lizenziert. Dieser Fehler ist nicht wiederherstellbar und wird als fatal behandelt.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Ein Netzwerkfehler ist aufgetreten. Bitte stellen Sie eine Internetverbindung her und versuchen Sie es erneut.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">Die installierte Version der Google Play-Dienste wurde auf diesem Gerät deaktiviert. Bitte schalten Sie die Google Play-Dienste ein.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">Die Version der auf diesem Gerät installierten Google Play-Dienste konnte nicht authentifiziert werden. Bitte Aktualisieren Sie die Google Play-Dienste im Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Google Play-Dienste fehlen auf diesem Gerät. Bitte installieren Sie die Google Play-Dienste über den Play Store.
</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">Die installierte Version der Google Play-Dienste ist veraltet. Aktualisieren Sie die Google Play-Dienste im Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Sie haben versucht, eine Verbindung mit dem Dienst herzustellen, aber Sie sind nicht angemeldet. Überprüfen Sie die Konfiguration der Google Play-Dienste</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Da dieses Gerät keinen Standortanbieter hat, kann diese App Ihren Standort nicht orten.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Der Standortdienst ist deaktiviert.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">Der Standortdienst wird vom Benutzer abgelehnt.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Sie konnten nicht lokalisiert werden. Versuchen Sie es bitte erneut.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-es\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="es"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Cerrar</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Por favor reemplace \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' en el archivo config.xml por su API Key!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">Por alguna razón Google Maps Android API v2 no está disponible en este dispositivo.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">La aplicación no está configurada correctamente. Ya que no es posible recuperarse de este error, será tratado como fatal. El desarrollador debe revisar los registros para determinar si existe alguna acción por realizar.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Ocurrió un error interno en Google Play Services. Por favor inténtalo de nuevo, y el problema debería resolverse.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Intentaste conectarte al servicio especificando un nombre de cuenta invalido.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">La aplicación no tiene licencia para el usuario. Ya que no es posible recuperarse de este error, será tratado como fatal.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Ocurrió un error de red. Por favor inténtalo de nuevo, y el problema debería resolverse.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled"> La versión instalada de Google Play Services ha sido deshabilitada en este dispositivo. Por favor encienda Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">La versión instalada de Google Play Services no es autentica. Por favor actualice Google Play Services desde Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">No se encontró Google Play Services en el dispositivo. Por favor instale Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">La versión instalada de Google Play services está desactualizada. Por favor actualice Google Play Services desde Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Intentaste conectarte a los servicios pero no has iniciado sesión. Por favor revisa la configuración de Google Play Services</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">En vista de que este dispositivo no tiene ningún proveedor de localización, la aplicación no puede detectar tu ubicación.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Servicio de localización desactivado.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">El servicio de localización fue rechazado por el usuario.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">No se pudo detectar tu ubicación. Inténtalo de nuevo.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-fr\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="fr"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Fermer</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Veuillez remplacer \"GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\" dans le fichier config.xml avec votre propre clé API!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">Google Maps Android API v2 n\'est pas disponible sur cet appareil pour une raison non identifiée.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">L\'application a mal été configurée. Cette erreur n\'est pas récupérable et sera traitée comme étant fatale. Le développeur devrait inspecter le journal d\'erreur afin de trouver des informations plus précises.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Une erreur interne est intervenue au niveau du Google Play Services. Veuillez réessayer, cela devrait résoudre le problème.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Vous avez tenté de vous connecter au service avec un nom de compte invalide.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">L\'application ne contient pas de licence pour cet utilisateur. Cette erreur n\'est pas récupérable et sera traitée comme étant fatale.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Un problème de réseau est intervenu. Veuillez réessayer, cela devrait résoudre le problème.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">La version du Google Play Services installée sur cet appareil a été désactivée. Veuillez activer le Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">La version du Google Play Services installée sur cet appareil n\'est pas authentique. Merci de mettre à jour le Google Play Services à partir du Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Google Play Services n\'est pas installé sur cet appareil. Merci d\'installer le Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">La version du Google Play Services installée sur cet appareil a expirée. Veuillez mettre à jour le Google Play Services à partir du Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Vous avez tenté de vous connecter au service, mais vous n\'est pas authentifié. Merci de vérifier la configuration du Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Cet appareil n\'est pas équipé d\'un service de localisation, cette application ne peut donc pas récupérer votre position.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Le service de localisation est désactivé.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">Le service de localisation est rejeté par l\'utilisateur.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Localisation introuvable. Veuillez réessayer.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-hi\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="hi"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">बंद</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">कृपया config.xml मे \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' को  अपनी  एपीआई कुंजी से बदलें</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">इस डिवाइस पर Google Maps Android API v2 उपलब्ध नहीं है</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">यह एप्लिकेशन गलत तरीके से कॉन्फ़िगर किया गया है. इस त्रुटि को ठीक किया नहीं जासकता इसे घातक माना जायेगा. डेवलपर को चाहिए वे लोग में देखकर कार्रवाई योग्य प्राप्त करे.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Google Play सेवाओं की एक आंतरिक त्रुटि हुई. कृप्या फिरसे प्रयास करें, इस से समस्या हल होनी चाहिए.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">आप ने एक अमान्य खाता नाम के साथ सेवा से जुड़ने का प्रयास है.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">इस उपयोगकर्ता के पास इस एप्लीकेशन लाइसेंस नहीं है. इस त्रुटि को ठीक किया नहीं जासकता इसे घातक माना जायेग.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">एक नेटवर्क त्रुटि हुई. कृप्या फिरसे प्रयास करें, इस से समस्या हल होनी चाहिए.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">इस डिवाइस पर Google Play सेवाओं का स्थापित संस्करण अक्षम है. कृपया Google Play सेवाएं चालू करें.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">इस डिवाइस पर स्थापित Google Play सेवाओं का संस्करण प्रामाणिक नहीं है. कृपया Google Play Store से Google Play सेवाएं अपडेट करें.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">इस डिवाइस पर Google Play सेवाएं मौजूद नहीं हैं. कृपया Google Play सेवाएं स्थापित करें.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">Google Play सेवाओं का स्थापित संस्करण पुराना है. कृपया Google Play Store से Google Play सेवाएं अपडेट करें.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">आप ने साइन किये बिना इस सेवा से जुड़ने का प्रयास किया है. कृपया Google Play सेवाएं कॉन्फ़िगरेशन जांचें</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">इस डिवाइस में कोई स्थान प्रदाता नहीं है, इसके कारण यह ऐप आपके स्थान का पता नहीं लगा सकता.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">स्थान सेवा अक्षम है.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">उपयोगकर्ता ने स्थान सेवा अस्वीकार कर दिया है.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">आप के स्थान का पता नही चल रहा है. कृप्या फिरसे प्रयास करें.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-ja\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="ja"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">閉じる</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">config.xmlファイル内の\'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\'をあなたのAPIキーに置き換えてください</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">この端末ではGoogle Maps Android API v2が利用できません。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">アプリケーションの設定が間違えています。このエラーは修復不可能かつ重大な失敗なものです。開発者は端末ログを確認してください。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Google Play Servicesの内部エラーが発生しました。おそらくもう一度試みていただければ解決します。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">ログインしているGoogleアカウントが不正です。再度ログインして試してみてください。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">このアプリケーションの使用がユーザーに認められていません。このエラーは修復不可能かつ重大な失敗なものです。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">ネットワークエラーが発生しました。おそらくもう一度試みていただければ解決します。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">この端末にインストールされているGoogle Play Servicesが無効になっています。Google Play Servicesを有効にしてください。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">この端末にインストールされているGoogle Play Servicesでは認証ができません。Google Play Storeから最新版のGoogle Play Servicesをインストールしてください。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">この端末にGoogle Play Servicesがインストールされていません。Google Play Storeから最新版のGoogle Play Servicesをインストールしてください。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">この端末にインストールされているGoogle Play Servicesが古過ぎです。Google Play Storeから最新版のGoogle Play Servicesをインストールしてください。</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Google Maps Android API v2を使用しようと試みましたが、あなたがGoogleアカウントにログインしていません。Googleアカウントにログインしてから再度試してみてください。</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">利用できる位置情報を取得できる方法(GPSなど)がないため、この端末の位置情報が取得できませんでした。</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">位置情報サービス(GPSなど)が無効になっています。</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">位置情報サービス(GPSなど)の利用がユーザーにより拒否されました。</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">この端末の位置情報が取得できませんでした。もう一度試してみてください。</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-nl\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="nl"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Sluiten</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Vervang \"GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\" in config.xml met je API Key!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">Google Maps Android API v2 is niet beschikbaar op dit apparaat.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">De applicatie is onjuist geconfigureerd. Deze foutmelding kan niet hesteld worden. De ontwikkelaar moet de logboek informatie bekijken om dit probleem op te lossen.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Er heeft een interne fout van Google Play Services plaatsgevonden. Probeer het opnieuw.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Je hebt geprobeerd om te verbinden met de service met een ongeldig gebruikersnaam.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">Er is geen licentie voor de gebruiker. Deze foutmelding kan niet hersteld worden.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Er heeft een netwerkfout plaatsgevonden. Probeer het opnieuw.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">De geinstalleerde versie van Google Play services staat uit op dit apparaat. Zet Google Play Services aan.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">De geinstaleerde versie van Google Play services is niet autentiek. Update Google Play Services van de Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Google Play services ontbreekt op dit apparaat. Installeer Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">De geinstalleerde Google Play services is niet langer geldig. Update Google Play Services van de Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Je probeert te verbinden met de service maar je bent niet ingelogd. Controleer de Google Play Services configuratie</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Omdat dit apparaat geen locatie provider heeft kan de app je locatie niet bepalen.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Locatie service staat uit.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">Locatie service is afgewezen door de gebruiker.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Kan je locatie niet bepalen. Probeer opnieuw.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-pl\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="pl"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Zamknij</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Proszę zastąpić \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' w pliku config.xml własnym kluczem API!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">Google Maps Android API v2 .</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">Aplikacja posiada niepoprawną konfigurację. Tego błędu nie można odtworzyć i będzie on traktowany jako krytyczny. W celu uzyskania bardziej szczegółowych informacji programista powinien przejrzeć pliki z logami.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Wystąpił błąd wewnątrz usług Google Play. Ponowne uruchomienie powinno rozwiązać problem.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Próbę nawiązania połączenia z usługą nie powiodła się, z powodu nieprawidłowej nazwy konta.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">Aplikacja nie jest licencjonowana dla użytkownika. Tego błędu nie można odtworzyć i będzie on traktowany jako krytyczny.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Wystąpił błąd połączenia internetowego. Proszę spróbować ponownie.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">Zainstalowana wersja usług Google Play została wyłączona na urządzeniu. Proszę włączyć  usługi Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">Zainstalowana na urządzeniu wersja usług Google Play jest fałszywa. Proszę zaktualizować usługi Google Play ze sklepu Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Nie odnaleziono zainstalowanej wersji usług Google Play. Proszę zainstalować  usługi Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">Zainstalowana wersja usług Google Play jest przestarzała. Proszę zaktualizować usługi Google Play Services w sklepie Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Próbowano połączyć się z usługami Google Play nie będąc zalogowanym. Proszę sprawdzić konfigurację usług Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Na urządzeniu nie odnaleziono usług dostarczających położenie. Aplikacja nie będzie w stanie określić położenia.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Usługi lokalizacji są wyłączone.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">Zgoda na usługi lokalizacji została odrzucona przez użytkownika.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Nie można określić położenia. Spróbuj ponownie.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-pt-rPT\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="pt-rPT"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Fechar</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Por favor substitua \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' em config.xml com sua chave de API!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">Google Maps Android API v2 não está disponível nesse dispositivo por alguma razão.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">O aplicativo está mal configurado. Este erro não é recuperável e será tratado como fatal. O desenvolvedor deve analisar os logs para determinar o que pode ser feito</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Ocorreu um erro interno no Google Play Services. Por favor tente novamente e o erro deverá estar resolvido.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Você tentou se conectar ao serviço com um nome de conta inválido.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">O aplicativo não está licenciado para o usuário. Esse erro não é recuperável e será tratado como fatal.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Ocorreu um erro de rede. Por favor tente novamente e o erro deverá estar resolvido.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">A versão instalada do Google Play Services foi desativada nesse dispositivo. Por favor ative o Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">A versão do Google Play Services instalada nesse dispositivo não é autêntica. Atualize o Google Play Services na Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">O Google Play services não existe nesse dispositivo. Por favor instale o Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">A versão do Google Play Services instalada está desatualizada. Por favor atualize o Google Play Services na Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Você tentou se conectar ao serviço mas você não está logado. Por favor cheque a configuração do Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Esse dispositivo não tem nenhum provedor de localização, logo, este aplicativo não pode detectar sua localização.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">O serviço de Localização está desativado.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">O serviço de Localização foi rejeitado pelo usuário.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Não foi possível detectar sua localização. Tente novamente.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-ru\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="ru"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Закрыть</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Пожалуйста, замените \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' в config.xml на Ваш API ключ!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">По какой то причине Google Maps Android API v2 не доступен на этом устройстве.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">Приложение неправильно настроено. Произошла фатальная ошибка. Разработчик приложения должен посмотреть в логи, чтобы исправить ошибку.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Произошла внутренняя ошибка Google Play Services. Пожалуйста, повторите попытку для решения проблемы.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Вы попытались подключиться к сервису с недопустимым именем учетной записи.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">Произошла фатальная ошибка. Приложение не лицензировано для этого пользователя.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Произошла сетевая ошибка. Пожалуйста, повторите попытку для решения проблемы.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">Установленная версия Google Play Services отключена на этом устройстве. Пожалуйста, включите Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">Версия Google Play Services установлена на этом уствройстве не подлинная. Пожалуйста, обновите Google Play Services из Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Google Play Services отсутствует на этом устройстве. Пожалуйста, установите Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">Установленная версия Google Play Services устаревшая. Пожалуйста, обновите Google Play Services из Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Вы попытались подключиться к сервису, но вы не вошли в систему. Пожалуйста, проверьте конфигурацию Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Поскольку это устройство не поддерживает поиск местоположения, это приложение не может определить Ваше расположение.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Сервис определения местоположения отключен.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">Определение местоположения отклонено пользователем.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Не удается определить Ваше местоположение. Попробуй еще раз.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-uk\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="uk"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Закрити</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Будь ласка, замініть \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' в config.xml на Ваш API ключ!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">По якісь причині Google Maps Android API v2 не доступний на цьому пристрої.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">Програма невірно налаштована. Виникла фатальна помилка. Розробник додатку повинен подивитись в логи, щоб виправити помилку.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Відбулася внутрішня помилка Google Play Services. Будь ласка, спробуйте ще раз для вирішення проблеми.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Ви спробували підключитися до сервісу з недійсним ім\'ям облікового запису.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">Виникла фатальна помилка. Додаток не ліцензійований для користувача.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Виникла помилка мережі. Будь ласка, спробуйте ще раз для вирішення проблеми.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">Встановлений Google Play Services на цьому пристрої - відключений. Будь ласка, увімкніть Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">Встановлена версія Google Play Services на цьому пристрої не є автентична. Будь ласка, обновіть Google Play Services із Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Google Play Services відсутній на цьому пристрої. Будь ласка, встановіть Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">Встановлена версія Google Play Services застаріла. Будь ласка, обновіть Google Play Services із Google Play Store.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Ви спробували підключитися до сервісу, але ви не ввійшли в систему. Будь ласка, перевірте конфігурацію Google Play Services.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Оскільки цей пристрій не підтримує пошук місцезнаходження, цей додаток не може визначити Ваше розташування.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Сервіс місцезнаходження вимкнений.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">Сервіс пошуку місцезнаходження відхилений користувачем.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Не вдається виявити Ваше місцезнаходження. Спробуйте знову.</string></file><file path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\main\res\values-vi\pgm_strings.xml" qualifiers="vi"><string name="pgm_google_close_button">Đóng</string><string name="pgm_api_key_error">Vui lòng thay \'GOOGLE_MAPS_ANDROID_API_KEY\' trong config.xml với API Key của bạn!</string><string name="pgm_google_play_error">Google Maps Android API v2 vì một lý do nào đó không hoạt động trên thiết bị của bạn.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_developer_error">Ứng dụng chưa được cấu hình. Lỗi này là nghiêm trọng và làm cho hệ thống ngừng hoạt động. Nhà phát triển cần kiểm tra hệ thống Logs để có hướng khắc phục cụ thể..</string><string name="pgm_google_play_internal_error">Lỗi xảy ra với dịch vụ Google Play. Vui lòng khởi động lại để hệ thống hoạt động bình thường..</string><string name="pgm_google_play_invalid_account">Bạn sử dụng tài khoản không hợp lệ để kết nối với dịch vụ.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_license_check_failed">Người sử dụng không được cấp phép sử dụng ứng dụng. Lỗi này là nghiêm trọng và làm cho hệ thống ngừng hoạt động.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_network_error">Đường truyền mạng có lỗi. Vui lòng thử lại, và hệ thống sẽ hoạt động bình thường.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_disabled">Dịch vụ Google Play không hoạt động trên thiết bị của bạn. Vui lòng bật dịch vụ Google Play để hệ thống hoạt động.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_invalid">Dịch vụ Google Play cài đặt trên máy của bạn không hợp lệ. Vui lòng cập nhật dịch vụ Google Play trên Kho ứng dụng Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_missing">Dịch vụ Google PLay chưa được cài đặt trên thiết bị của bạn. Vui lòng cài đặt dịch vụ Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_service_update_required">Dịch vụ Google Play của bạn đã lỗi thời. Vui lòng cập nhật dịch vụ Google Play trên Kho ứng dụng Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_google_play_sign_in_required">Bạn chưa thực hiện đăng nhập để kết nối với dịch vụ. Vui lòng xem lại cấu hình dịch vụ Google Play.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_providers">Thiết bị không hỗ trợ xác định vị trí vì vậy ứng dụng không thể xác định vị trí của bạn.</string><string name="pgm_no_location_service_is_disabled">Dịch vụ xác định vị trí không được kích hoạt.</string><string name="pgm_location_rejected_by_user">Người dùng không cho phép sử dụng dịch vụ xác định vị trí.</string><string name="pgm_can_not_get_location">Không thể xác định vị trí của bạn. Vui lòng thử lại..</string></file></source><source path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\build\generated\res\rs\debug"/><source path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\build\generated\res\resValues\debug"/></dataSet><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="debug$Generated" generated="true" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~"><source path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\debug\res"/></dataSet><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="debug" generated-set="debug$Generated" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~"><source path="C:\Project\park-n-go\android\capacitor-cordova-android-plugins\src\debug\res"/></dataSet><mergedItems/></merger>